

Email: <u>fynstarr96@gmail.com</u>
*Please email me for other contact information.

Personal Profile

I am a friendly person who has excellent customer service skills that have been developed over a wide range of customer facing roles, which allows me to remain focused and empathetic while remaining professional when dealing with customer complaints. I have extensive knowledge with computers and am able to learn most systems quickly and confidently. Being an organised person I am able to prioritise my work efficiently, completing tasks within deadlines and with a high attention to detail. From various work experience I have been able to develop my skills so that I am able to work well in a team and on my own.

Education

- Information Technology, Distinction.
- Drama, B.
- Music, B.
- Certificate of Personal Effectiveness, Level 2/ B GCSE Equivalent.
- English, C.
- Maths, C.

Skills

- Customer Facing Engaging positively with customers in any situation.
- Quick Learner Learning new systems, ways of working, and policies.
- Practical I enjoy finding solutions to problems, and do so in a logical manner.
- Computer Literate I am very familiar with computers, and have used Windows and Linux operating systems for personal use for several years.

Key Employment History

The Big Word | Link Up House, Ring Rd, Leeds, LS12 6AB Interpreting Coordinator | September 2019 - Present

Capita | Hepworth House, Clay Pit Ln, Leeds, LS2 8AE Customer Service Advisor | November 2017 - June 2018

Vodafone | The White House, Melbourne St, Leeds, LS2 7PS Customer Service Advisor | January 2016 - July 2016 Fyn Starr

. . .

Thank you for taking the time to view my CV. I look forward to hearing from you soon.